<alps version="1.0"
      xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://alps-io.github.io/schemas/alps.xsd">
    <title>Learning Management System (LMS)</title>
    <doc>A comprehensive ALPS (Application-Level Profile Semantics) profile that defines the complete semantic vocabulary and interaction model for an enterprise-grade Learning Management System. This specification covers all aspects of online education including user management (students, instructors, administrators), course creation and delivery, content management, assessments, grading, communication tools, collaboration features, analytics, and accessibility. The profile is organized into semantic descriptors, state transitions, and navigation patterns to support standardized implementation and interoperability across educational technology platforms.</doc>
    <!-- SECTION 1: SEMANTIC DEFINITIONS (ONTOLOGY) -->

    <!-- Core User Types -->
    <descriptor id="user" title="User" def="https://schema.org/Person" tag="core user">
        <doc>Represents a person who interacts with the Learning Management System. Users can have different roles including student, instructor, or administrator. Each user has a unique identifier, personal details, and system preferences.</doc>
        <descriptor id="userId" title="User Identifier" def="https://schema.org/identifier" tag="core user">
            <doc>A unique identifier for the user, typically an alphanumeric string that serves as the primary key in the database.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="userName" title="User Name" def="https://schema.org/name" tag="core user">
            <doc>The full name of the user, typically comprising first name and last name. Used for display purposes throughout the system.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="userEmail" title="User Email" def="https://schema.org/email" tag="core user contact">
            <doc>The email address associated with the user account. Used for system notifications, password recovery, and as the username for login.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="userPassword" title="User Password" tag="core user security">
            <doc>The password for user authentication. Should be stored using strong encryption algorithms and subject to complexity requirements.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="userRole" title="User Role" tag="core user authorization">
            <doc>Defines the permissions and access level of the user within the system. Common roles include student, instructor, and administrator.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="userPreferences" title="User Preferences" tag="core user personalization">
            <doc>User-specific settings including interface preferences, notification settings, and accessibility options that customize the user experience.</doc>
        </descriptor>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="student" title="Student" tag="user education" doc="Individual who registers for courses, accesses content, and submits assignments. The primary consumer of educational content who enrolls in courses, completes assignments, participates in discussions, and receives grades.">
        <descriptor id="enrolledCourses" title="Enrolled Courses" tag="education enrollment">
            <doc>The collection of courses in which the student is currently enrolled. Includes active, completed, and upcoming courses.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="progress" title="Learning Progress" tag="education tracking">
            <doc>Metrics and indicators that track the student's advancement through course materials, including completion status of content items, modules, and assessments.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="grades" title="Student Grades" tag="education assessment">
            <doc>Collection of evaluation scores received by the student for assignments, quizzes, exams, and participation across all enrolled courses.</doc>
        </descriptor>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="instructor" title="Instructor" tag="user education teaching" doc="Educator who creates and manages courses, evaluates student progress. Responsible for developing course content, designing assessments, facilitating discussions, and evaluating student performance.">
        <descriptor id="taughtCourses" title="Courses Taught" tag="education teaching">
            <doc>Collection of courses created or taught by the instructor, including current, past, and planned courses.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="instructorExpertise" title="Areas of Expertise" tag="education teaching">
            <doc>Subject areas and disciplines in which the instructor specializes, used for instructor discovery and course categorization.</doc>
        </descriptor>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="administrator" title="Administrator" tag="user admin" doc="Person who oversees the entire system, manages user accounts and course catalog. Has elevated privileges to configure system settings, manage users, and generate institutional reports.">
        <descriptor id="adminPermissions" title="Administrative Permissions" tag="admin security">
            <doc>Specific system capabilities assigned to the administrator, which may include user management, course approval, analytics access, and system configuration options.</doc>
        </descriptor>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Course Related -->
    <descriptor id="course" title="Course" def="https://schema.org/Course" tag="education content">
        <doc>The primary unit of instruction within the LMS. A structured educational experience with defined learning objectives, content modules, assessments, and timeline. Courses are created by instructors and taken by students.</doc>
        <descriptor id="courseId" title="Course Identifier" def="https://schema.org/identifier" tag="education core">
            <doc>A unique identifier for the course, used as a reference key throughout the system.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="courseTitle" title="Course Title" def="https://schema.org/name" tag="education content">
            <doc>The name of the course as displayed in the catalog and to enrolled users. Should be descriptive and specific.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="courseDescription" title="Course Description" def="https://schema.org/description" tag="education content">
            <doc>An extended explanation of the course content, learning objectives, and expected outcomes. Displayed to potential students during course discovery and selection.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="courseCategory" title="Course Category" def="https://schema.org/courseCategory" tag="education taxonomy">
            <doc>The subject category or discipline to which the course belongs, used for organization and discovery within the course catalog.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="startDate" title="Start Date" def="https://schema.org/startDate" tag="education scheduling">
            <doc>The date when the course becomes available to enrolled students, marking the beginning of the learning period.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="endDate" title="End Date" def="https://schema.org/endDate" tag="education scheduling">
            <doc>The date when the course closes, after which new submissions may not be accepted and course content may become inaccessible.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="enrollmentCapacity" title="Enrollment Capacity" def="https://schema.org/maximumEnrollment" tag="education administration">
            <doc>The maximum number of students who can enroll in the course. Used to manage class size and resource allocation.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="difficultyLevel" title="Difficulty Level" tag="education content">
            <doc>An indicator of the course's complexity and required prior knowledge, such as introductory, intermediate, advanced, or expert.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="courseStatus" title="Course Status" tag="education administration">
            <doc>The current state of the course in its lifecycle, which may include draft, published, in-progress, completed, or archived.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="prerequisites" title="Prerequisites" tag="education content">
            <doc>Other courses or qualifications that students should complete before enrolling in this course, ensuring appropriate preparation.</doc>
        </descriptor>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="module" title="Course Module" tag="education content structure" doc="Section of a course to organize content in logical order. A thematic unit within a course that groups related content items, activities, and assessments into a cohesive learning sequence.">
        <descriptor id="moduleId" title="Module Identifier" tag="education core">
            <doc>A unique identifier for the module, used for reference within the system and to track completion status.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="moduleTitle" title="Module Title" def="https://schema.org/name" tag="education content">
            <doc>The name of the module as displayed to users, indicating the subject matter or themes covered.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="moduleDescription" title="Module Description" def="https://schema.org/description" tag="education content">
            <doc>A summary of the module's learning objectives, content, and activities, helping students understand its purpose and structure.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="moduleOrder" title="Module Order" tag="education structure">
            <doc>The sequence number that determines the module's position within the course structure, defining the recommended learning path.</doc>
        </descriptor>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="content" title="Course Content" tag="education content media" doc="Teaching materials in various formats. Educational resources used for instruction, including text, multimedia, interactive activities, and downloadable files.">
        <descriptor id="contentId" title="Content Identifier" tag="education core">
            <doc>A unique identifier for the content item, used for reference and tracking within the system.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="contentTitle" title="Content Title" def="https://schema.org/name" tag="education content">
            <doc>The name of the content item as displayed to users, indicating its subject or purpose.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="contentDescription" title="Content Description" def="https://schema.org/description" tag="education content">
            <doc>A summary of the content's purpose, format, and learning objectives, helping students understand its relevance.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="contentType" title="Content Type" tag="education media">
            <doc>The format of the content, such as text, video, audio, presentation, interactive simulation, or downloadable file.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="contentData" title="Content Data" tag="education media">
            <doc>The actual content material, which may be embedded within the system or linked from external sources.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="contentStatus" title="Content Status" tag="education workflow" doc="Draft or published">
            <doc>The current state of the content item, indicating whether it is in development (draft) or available to students (published).</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="contentAccessibility" title="Content Accessibility Features" tag="education accessibility">
            <doc>Accommodations and design elements that ensure content is usable by students with disabilities, such as alt text, captions, or screen reader compatibility.</doc>
        </descriptor>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Assessment Related -->
    <descriptor id="assignment" title="Assignment" tag="education assessment" doc="Task assigned to students to assess learning. An evaluation activity that requires students to demonstrate knowledge, skills, or competencies related to course objectives.">
        <descriptor id="assignmentId" title="Assignment Identifier" tag="education core">
            <doc>A unique identifier for the assignment, used for reference and tracking within the system.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="assignmentTitle" title="Assignment Title" def="https://schema.org/name" tag="education assessment">
            <doc>The name of the assignment as displayed to users, indicating its subject or purpose.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="assignmentDescription" title="Assignment Description" def="https://schema.org/description" tag="education assessment">
            <doc>Detailed instructions for completing the assignment, including requirements, format, and evaluation criteria.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="assignmentType" title="Assignment Type" tag="education assessment">
            <doc>The category of assessment, such as essay, quiz, exam, project, discussion, or practical exercise.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="dueDate" title="Due Date" def="https://schema.org/endDate" tag="education scheduling">
            <doc>The deadline by which students must submit their work, after which late penalties may apply or submissions may be rejected.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="maxScore" title="Maximum Score" tag="education assessment">
            <doc>The highest possible points or grade that can be earned for the assignment, establishing the scoring scale.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="weightage" title="Weightage in Overall Grade" tag="education assessment">
            <doc>The percentage or proportion of the final course grade determined by this assignment.</doc>
        </descriptor>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="submission" title="Assignment Submission" tag="education assessment student" doc="Student's response to an assignment. The work provided by a student in fulfillment of an assignment's requirements, which may include text, files, or other digital artifacts.">
        <descriptor id="submissionId" title="Submission Identifier" tag="education core">
            <doc>A unique identifier for the submission, used for reference and tracking within the system.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="submissionContent" title="Submission Content" tag="education assessment">
            <doc>The actual work submitted by the student, which may include text entries, uploaded files, or links to external resources.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="submissionDate" title="Submission Date" def="https://schema.org/dateCreated" tag="education tracking">
            <doc>The date and time when the submission was received by the system, used to verify timeliness relative to deadlines.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="submissionStatus" title="Submission Status" tag="education workflow">
            <doc>The current state of the submission in the grading workflow, such as submitted, under review, graded, or returned for revision.</doc>
        </descriptor>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="grade" title="Grade" tag="education assessment evaluation" doc="Evaluation of a student's submission. An assessment of the quality, correctness, or achievement level of a student's work on an assignment.">
        <descriptor id="gradeId" title="Grade Identifier" tag="education core">
            <doc>A unique identifier for the grade record, used for reference and tracking within the system.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="gradeValue" title="Grade Value" tag="education assessment">
            <doc>The score or evaluation assigned to the submission, which may be numeric, letter-based, or categorical (pass/fail).</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="feedback" title="Feedback" tag="education assessment">
            <doc>Comments, corrections, and guidance provided by the instructor to help the student understand the evaluation and improve future work.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="gradedDate" title="Graded Date" tag="education tracking">
            <doc>The date and time when the grade was assigned, used for tracking grading timelines and notification purposes.</doc>
        </descriptor>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="rubric" title="Grading Rubric" tag="education assessment evaluation" doc="Criteria for evaluating student work. A structured scoring tool that defines performance expectations across multiple dimensions of an assignment.">
        <descriptor id="rubricId" title="Rubric Identifier" tag="education core">
            <doc>A unique identifier for the rubric, used for reference and tracking within the system.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="rubricTitle" title="Rubric Title" tag="education assessment">
            <doc>The name of the rubric as displayed to users, often indicating the assignment or type of assessment it supports.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="rubricCriteria" title="Rubric Criteria" tag="education assessment">
            <doc>The specific dimensions and performance levels used for evaluation, with descriptions of expectations at each level.</doc>
        </descriptor>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Communication Related -->
    <descriptor id="discussion" title="Discussion Forum" tag="communication collaboration" doc="Platform for questions and answers. An interactive space where course participants can engage in threaded conversations about course topics or ask questions.">
        <descriptor id="discussionId" title="Discussion Identifier" tag="communication core">
            <doc>A unique identifier for the discussion forum, used for reference and tracking within the system.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="discussionTitle" title="Discussion Title" def="https://schema.org/name" tag="communication">
            <doc>The name of the discussion forum as displayed to users, indicating its topic or purpose.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="discussionDescription" title="Discussion Description" def="https://schema.org/description" tag="communication">
            <doc>An explanation of the forum's purpose, guidelines, and expectations for participation.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="posts" title="Discussion Posts" tag="communication">
            <doc>The collection of messages contributed to the discussion by participants, organized in chronological or threaded format.</doc>
        </descriptor>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="post" title="Discussion Post" tag="communication collaboration" doc="Message in a discussion forum. A contribution to a discussion forum that may initiate a new thread or respond to an existing message.">
        <descriptor id="postId" title="Post Identifier" tag="communication core">
            <doc>A unique identifier for the post, used for reference and tracking within the system.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="postContent" title="Post Content" def="https://schema.org/text" tag="communication">
            <doc>The text of the message, which may include formatting, links, or embedded media.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="postDate" title="Post Date" def="https://schema.org/dateCreated" tag="communication tracking">
            <doc>The date and time when the post was created, used for chronological organization and activity tracking.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="postAuthor" title="Post Author" def="https://schema.org/author" tag="communication user">
            <doc>The user who created the post, displayed alongside the content for attribution.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="replies" title="Post Replies" tag="communication">
            <doc>Responses to the post from other users, creating a nested conversation thread.</doc>
        </descriptor>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="notification" title="Notification" tag="communication alerts" doc="System message to inform users. An automatic communication from the LMS to alert users about relevant events, deadlines, or updates.">
        <descriptor id="notificationId" title="Notification Identifier" tag="communication core">
            <doc>A unique identifier for the notification, used for reference and tracking within the system.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="notificationContent" title="Notification Content" tag="communication">
            <doc>The message body of the notification, explaining the event or information being communicated.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="notificationType" title="Notification Type" tag="communication">
            <doc>The category of notification, such as announcement, deadline reminder, grade posting, or system alert.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="notificationDate" title="Notification Date" def="https://schema.org/dateCreated" tag="communication tracking">
            <doc>The date and time when the notification was generated, used for chronological organization.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="notificationStatus" title="Notification Status" tag="communication">
            <doc>The current state of the notification, such as unread, read, or dismissed, tracking user interaction.</doc>
        </descriptor>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="message" title="Direct Message" tag="communication personal" doc="Private communication between users. A confidential exchange between specific system users, not visible to others.">
        <descriptor id="messageId" title="Message Identifier" tag="communication core">
            <doc>A unique identifier for the message, used for reference and tracking within the system.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="messageContent" title="Message Content" def="https://schema.org/text" tag="communication">
            <doc>The text of the message, which may include formatting, links, or embedded media.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="messageDate" title="Message Date" def="https://schema.org/dateCreated" tag="communication tracking">
            <doc>The date and time when the message was sent, used for chronological organization.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="messageSender" title="Message Sender" tag="communication user">
            <doc>The user who initiated the message, displayed for attribution.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="messageRecipient" title="Message Recipient" tag="communication user">
            <doc>The user or users designated to receive the message, controlling its visibility.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="messageAttachments" title="Message Attachments" tag="communication media">
            <doc>Files or references included with the message, such as documents, images, or links.</doc>
        </descriptor>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="group" title="Student Group" tag="collaboration" doc="Collection of students for collaboration. A defined subset of course participants who work together on assignments or activities.">
        <descriptor id="groupId" title="Group Identifier" tag="collaboration core">
            <doc>A unique identifier for the group, used for reference and tracking within the system.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="groupName" title="Group Name" def="https://schema.org/name" tag="collaboration">
            <doc>The name of the group as displayed to users, often chosen by members or assigned by instructors.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="groupMembers" title="Group Members" tag="collaboration users">
            <doc>The collection of students assigned to the group, who can collaborate on shared activities.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="groupWorkspace" title="Shared Workspace" tag="collaboration">
            <doc>A dedicated area where group members can communicate, share files, and collaborate on activities privately within the group.</doc>
        </descriptor>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="webinar" title="Online Session" tag="communication synchronous" doc="Real-time virtual class session. A scheduled live event where instructors and students interact simultaneously through video, audio, chat, or shared screens.">
        <descriptor id="webinarId" title="Webinar Identifier" tag="communication core">
            <doc>A unique identifier for the webinar, used for reference and tracking within the system.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="webinarTitle" title="Webinar Title" def="https://schema.org/name" tag="communication">
            <doc>The name of the webinar as displayed to users, indicating its topic or purpose.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="webinarDescription" title="Webinar Description" def="https://schema.org/description" tag="communication">
            <doc>An explanation of the webinar's content, objectives, and participation requirements.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="webinarDate" title="Webinar Date" def="https://schema.org/startDate" tag="communication scheduling">
            <doc>The date and time when the webinar will begin, used for scheduling and reminders.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="webinarDuration" title="Webinar Duration" def="https://schema.org/duration" tag="communication scheduling">
            <doc>The expected length of the session, helping participants plan their attendance.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="webinarUrl" title="Webinar URL" def="https://schema.org/url" tag="communication">
            <doc>The web address for joining the online session, which may link to a video conferencing platform.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="webinarRecording" title="Webinar Recording" tag="communication media">
            <doc>A captured video of the session made available for later viewing by those who couldn't attend live or want to review.</doc>
        </descriptor>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Analytics Related -->
    <descriptor id="analytics" title="User Analytics" tag="analytics tracking" doc="Data on user engagement and activity. Metrics that track how users interact with the system, providing insights into learning behaviors and platform usage.">
        <descriptor id="loginFrequency" title="Login Frequency" tag="analytics engagement">
            <doc>How often users access the system, measured as logins per time period, indicating engagement levels.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="contentViewed" title="Content Viewed" tag="analytics engagement">
            <doc>Records of which content items users have accessed, tracking exposure to course materials.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="timeSpent" title="Time Spent on Platform" tag="analytics engagement">
            <doc>Duration of user sessions, measured in minutes or hours, indicating depth of engagement.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="assignmentCompletionTime" title="Time to Complete Assignments" tag="analytics performance">
            <doc>How long users take to finish assignments, measured from first view to submission, indicating effort levels.</doc>
        </descriptor>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="report" title="System Report" tag="analytics administration" doc="Aggregated data for analysis. A structured compilation of system data organized for specific analysis purposes, often used by administrators for decision-making.">
        <descriptor id="reportId" title="Report Identifier" tag="analytics core">
            <doc>A unique identifier for the report, used for reference and tracking within the system.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="reportTitle" title="Report Title" tag="analytics">
            <doc>The name of the report as displayed to users, indicating its content or purpose.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="reportType" title="Report Type" tag="analytics">
            <doc>The category of report, such as usage statistics, grade distribution, completion rates, or financial summary.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="reportData" title="Report Data" tag="analytics">
            <doc>The actual information contained in the report, which may include tables, charts, or raw data exports.</doc>
        </descriptor>
        <descriptor id="reportDate" title="Report Generation Date" def="https://schema.org/dateCreated" tag="analytics tracking">
            <doc>The date and time when the report was created, important for temporal context of the data.</doc>
        </descriptor>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Accessibility & Mobile -->
    <descriptor id="language" title="Interface Language" def="https://schema.org/inLanguage" tag="accessibility localization">
        <doc>The selected language for system text and communications, allowing users to interact with the LMS in their preferred language.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="accessibilityFeature" title="Accessibility Feature" def="https://schema.org/accessibilityFeature" tag="accessibility">
        <doc>Functions that improve usability for users with disabilities, such as screen reader support, keyboard navigation, high contrast modes, or text resizing options.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="offlineContent" title="Offline Content" tag="mobile access" doc="Downloaded content for access without internet. Course materials that have been saved locally to a device for use when connectivity is limited or unavailable.">
        <doc>Course materials that students can download to their devices for viewing without an active internet connection, supporting learning in low-connectivity situations.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- SECTION 2: CONTAINMENT RELATIONSHIPS (TAXONOMY) -->

    <!-- Main Application States -->
    <descriptor id="Home" title="Home Page" tag="navigation dashboard" doc="System landing page. The primary entry point for authenticated users, displaying personalized navigation, notifications, and activity summaries.">
        <descriptor href="#course"/>
        <descriptor href="#notification"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCourseList"/>
        <descriptor href="#goUserProfile"/>
        <descriptor href="#goMessageCenter"/>
        <descriptor href="#goNotifications"/>
        <descriptor href="#goSettings"/>
        <descriptor href="#goReportCenter"/>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- User Management States -->
    <descriptor id="Login" title="Login Page" tag="user-management authentication">
        <doc>The entry point for user authentication where existing users provide credentials to access the system.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#userEmail"/>
        <descriptor href="#userPassword"/>
        <descriptor href="#doLogin"/>
        <descriptor href="#goRegister"/>
        <descriptor href="#doResetPassword"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="Register" title="Registration Page" tag="user-management enrollment">
        <doc>The interface where new users create accounts by providing personal information and selecting their role within the system.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#userName"/>
        <descriptor href="#userEmail"/>
        <descriptor href="#userPassword"/>
        <descriptor href="#userRole"/>
        <descriptor href="#doRegister"/>
        <descriptor href="#goLogin"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="UserProfile" title="User Profile Page" tag="user-management personalization">
        <doc>The interface where users can view and edit their personal information, preferences, and system settings.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#user"/>
        <descriptor href="#doUpdateProfile"/>
        <descriptor href="#goHome"/>
        <descriptor href="#goEnrolledCourses"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="UserList" title="User Management Page" tag="user-management admin-tools">
        <doc>An administrative interface that displays all system users and provides tools for account management and permission assignment.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#user"/>
        <descriptor href="#doCreateUser"/>
        <descriptor href="#doDeleteUser"/>
        <descriptor href="#doUpdateUser"/>
        <descriptor href="#goUserDetail"/>
        <descriptor href="#goHome"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="UserDetail" title="User Details Page" tag="user-management admin-tools">
        <doc>An administrative interface that displays comprehensive information about a specific user, including their permissions and activity history.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#user"/>
        <descriptor href="#doUpdateUser"/>
        <descriptor href="#doDeleteUser"/>
        <descriptor href="#goUserList"/>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Course Management States -->
    <descriptor id="CourseList" title="Course Listing Page" tag="course-management catalog">
        <doc>An interface that displays available courses, with filtering and sorting options to help users discover relevant educational opportunities.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#course"/>
        <descriptor href="#goFilterCourses"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCourseDetail"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCreateCourse"/>
        <descriptor href="#goHome"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="CourseDetail" title="Course Details Page" tag="course-management content">
        <doc>A comprehensive view of a specific course, displaying its structure, content, activities, and participant information.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#course"/>
        <descriptor href="#module"/>
        <descriptor href="#assignment"/>
        <descriptor href="#discussion"/>
        <descriptor href="#instructor"/>
        <descriptor href="#doEnrollCourse"/>
        <descriptor href="#goModuleDetail"/>
        <descriptor href="#goAssignmentList"/>
        <descriptor href="#goDiscussionList"/>
        <descriptor href="#goEditCourse"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCourseList"/>
        <descriptor href="#goProgressDashboard"/>
        <descriptor href="#goWebinarSchedule"/>
        <descriptor href="#goAnalyticsDashboard"/>
        <descriptor href="#goAnnouncementCreation"/>
        <descriptor href="#goGradebook"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="CourseCreation" title="Course Creation Page" tag="course-management authoring">
        <doc>An interface where instructors define new courses by specifying details, structure, and settings before publishing to the catalog.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#course"/>
        <descriptor href="#doCreateCourse"/>
        <descriptor href="#doSaveDraftCourse"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCourseList"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="CourseEdit" title="Course Edit Page" tag="course-management authoring">
        <doc>An interface where instructors modify existing courses, updating content, structure, or settings as needed.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#course"/>
        <descriptor href="#doUpdateCourse"/>
        <descriptor href="#doDeleteCourse"/>
        <descriptor href="#doSaveDraftCourse"/>
        <descriptor href="#doPublishCourse"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCourseDetail"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="ModuleList" title="Course Modules Page" tag="course-management structure">
        <doc>An interface that displays all modules within a course, showing their sequence and allowing for management operations.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#module"/>
        <descriptor href="#doCreateModule"/>
        <descriptor href="#goModuleDetail"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCourseDetail"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="ModuleDetail" title="Module Details Page" tag="course-management content">
        <doc>A comprehensive view of a specific module, displaying its content items, structure, and allowing for management operations.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#module"/>
        <descriptor href="#content"/>
        <descriptor href="#doUpdateModule"/>
        <descriptor href="#doDeleteModule"/>
        <descriptor href="#goContentDetail"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCreateContent"/>
        <descriptor href="#goModuleList"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="ContentCreation" title="Content Creation Page" tag="content-creation authoring">
        <doc>An interface where instructors create educational materials by selecting content types and creating or uploading learning resources.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#content"/>
        <descriptor href="#contentType"/>
        <descriptor href="#contentAccessibility"/>
        <descriptor href="#doCreateContent"/>
        <descriptor href="#doSaveDraftContent"/>
        <descriptor href="#goPreviewContent"/>
        <descriptor href="#goModuleDetail"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="ContentDetail" title="Content Detail Page" tag="content-creation management">
        <doc>A comprehensive view of a specific content item, displaying its details and allowing for management operations such as editing or removal.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#content"/>
        <descriptor href="#doUpdateContent"/>
        <descriptor href="#doDeleteContent"/>
        <descriptor href="#goPreviewContent"/>
        <descriptor href="#goModuleDetail"/>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Enrollment and Progress States -->
    <descriptor id="EnrolledCourses" title="Enrolled Courses Page" tag="enrollment student">
        <doc>A personalized view for students showing all courses they are currently registered for, with status indicators and navigation options.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#course"/>
        <descriptor href="#progress"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCourseDetail"/>
        <descriptor href="#goHome"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="ProgressDashboard" title="Learning Progress Dashboard" tag="progress-tracking student">
        <doc>A visual display of a student's advancement through course materials, showing completion status, scores, and time spent across modules.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#course"/>
        <descriptor href="#module"/>
        <descriptor href="#progress"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCourseDetail"/>
        <descriptor href="#goModuleDetail"/>
        <descriptor href="#goEnrolledCourses"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="ClassProgress" title="Class Progress Dashboard" tag="progress-tracking instructor-tools">
        <doc>An overview for instructors showing all students' advancement and performance in a course, highlighting areas of success or concern.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#student"/>
        <descriptor href="#course"/>
        <descriptor href="#progress"/>
        <descriptor href="#goFilterStudents"/>
        <descriptor href="#goStudentProgress"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCourseDetail"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="StudentProgress" title="Individual Student Progress" tag="progress-tracking instructor-tools">
        <doc>A detailed view for instructors of a specific student's performance and engagement across all course activities and assessments.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#student"/>
        <descriptor href="#course"/>
        <descriptor href="#module"/>
        <descriptor href="#progress"/>
        <descriptor href="#doExtendDeadline"/>
        <descriptor href="#goClassProgress"/>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Assessment States -->
    <descriptor id="AssignmentList" title="Course Assignments Page" tag="assessment course-management">
        <doc>A listing of all evaluation activities for a course, organized chronologically or by type, with status indicators and management options.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#assignment"/>
        <descriptor href="#goFilterAssignments"/>
        <descriptor href="#goAssignmentDetail"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCreateAssignment"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCourseDetail"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="AssignmentCreation" title="Assignment Creation Page" tag="assessment authoring">
        <doc>An interface where instructors define new evaluation activities by specifying requirements, due dates, and grading criteria.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#assignment"/>
        <descriptor href="#assignmentType"/>
        <descriptor href="#rubric"/>
        <descriptor href="#doCreateAssignment"/>
        <descriptor href="#doCreateRubric"/>
        <descriptor href="#goAssignmentList"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="AssignmentDetail" title="Assignment Details Page" tag="assessment">
        <doc>A comprehensive view of a specific assignment, showing its requirements, deadlines, submission status, and available actions.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#assignment"/>
        <descriptor href="#rubric"/>
        <descriptor href="#submission"/>
        <descriptor href="#doUpdateAssignment"/>
        <descriptor href="#doDeleteAssignment"/>
        <descriptor href="#doSubmitAssignment"/>
        <descriptor href="#goSubmissionList"/>
        <descriptor href="#goAssignmentList"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="SubmissionList" title="Assignment Submissions Page" tag="assessment grading instructor-tools">
        <doc>A listing for instructors of all student responses to an assignment, showing submission status, timestamps, and grading progress.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#submission"/>
        <descriptor href="#goFilterSubmissions"/>
        <descriptor href="#goSubmissionDetail"/>
        <descriptor href="#goAssignmentDetail"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="SubmissionDetail" title="Submission Detail Page" tag="assessment grading instructor-tools">
        <doc>A comprehensive view of a specific student's assignment response, with tools for evaluation, feedback, and grade assignment.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#submission"/>
        <descriptor href="#grade"/>
        <descriptor href="#feedback"/>
        <descriptor href="#rubric"/>
        <descriptor href="#doGradeSubmission"/>
        <descriptor href="#doProvideFeedback"/>
        <descriptor href="#goSubmissionList"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="Gradebook" title="Course Gradebook" tag="assessment grading instructor-tools">
        <doc>A comprehensive record of all student evaluations for a course, showing scores across assignments and calculated overall grades.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#student"/>
        <descriptor href="#assignment"/>
        <descriptor href="#grade"/>
        <descriptor href="#doExportGrades"/>
        <descriptor href="#doCalculateOverallGrades"/>
        <descriptor href="#goSubmissionDetail"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCourseDetail"/>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Communication States -->
    <descriptor id="DiscussionList" title="Course Discussions Page" tag="communication collaboration">
        <doc>A listing of all conversation forums for a course, organized by topic or activity level, with creation and participation options.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#discussion"/>
        <descriptor href="#goFilterDiscussions"/>
        <descriptor href="#goDiscussionDetail"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCreateDiscussion"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCourseDetail"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="DiscussionDetail" title="Discussion Thread Page" tag="communication collaboration">
        <doc>A view of a specific conversation forum, showing all posts in threaded or chronological order with tools for participation.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#discussion"/>
        <descriptor href="#post"/>
        <descriptor href="#doCreatePost"/>
        <descriptor href="#doReplyToPost"/>
        <descriptor href="#goDiscussionList"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="External" title="External System" tag="integration" doc="Represents an external system or URL outside the LMS. A connection point to third-party tools, resources, or platforms that integrate with the learning system.">
        <doc>A reference to services outside the LMS that have been integrated for functions like video conferencing, specialized simulations, or external content repositories.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="AnnouncementCreation" title="Create Announcement Page" tag="communication instructor-tools">
        <doc>An interface where instructors compose system messages to be broadcast to all course participants, with options for timing and distribution.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#notification"/>
        <descriptor href="#doCreateAnnouncement"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCourseDetail"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="MessageCenter" title="Messaging Center" tag="communication personal">
        <doc>A unified inbox for personal communications within the system, showing messages exchanged with other users in conversation threads.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#message"/>
        <descriptor href="#goFilterMessages"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCreateMessage"/>
        <descriptor href="#goMessageDetail"/>
        <descriptor href="#goHome"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="MessageDetail" title="Message Detail Page" tag="communication personal">
        <doc>A view of a specific message exchange, showing the conversation history and providing tools for response and attachment handling.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#message"/>
        <descriptor href="#doReplyToMessage"/>
        <descriptor href="#doAttachFile"/>
        <descriptor href="#goMessageCenter"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="GroupManagement" title="Group Management Page" tag="collaboration instructor-tools">
        <doc>An interface for creating and organizing student teams within a course, with tools for membership assignment and workspace configuration.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#group"/>
        <descriptor href="#doCreateGroup"/>
        <descriptor href="#doUpdateGroup"/>
        <descriptor href="#doDeleteGroup"/>
        <descriptor href="#goGroupDetail"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCourseDetail"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="GroupDetail" title="Group Detail Page" tag="collaboration">
        <doc>A comprehensive view of a specific student team, showing its members, shared resources, and collaboration spaces with management options.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#group"/>
        <descriptor href="#groupWorkspace"/>
        <descriptor href="#doAddGroupMember"/>
        <descriptor href="#doRemoveGroupMember"/>
        <descriptor href="#goGroupManagement"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="WebinarSchedule" title="Webinar Schedule Page" tag="communication synchronous instructor-tools">
        <doc>A calendar view of planned live sessions for a course, with creation, management, and participation options for virtual meetings.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#webinar"/>
        <descriptor href="#doCreateWebinar"/>
        <descriptor href="#doUpdateWebinar"/>
        <descriptor href="#doDeleteWebinar"/>
        <descriptor href="#goWebinarDetail"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCourseDetail"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="WebinarDetail" title="Webinar Detail Page" tag="communication synchronous">
        <doc>A comprehensive view of a specific live session, showing its details, participation link, and recording access with relevant actions.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#webinar"/>
        <descriptor href="#webinarRecording"/>
        <descriptor href="#doJoinWebinar"/>
        <descriptor href="#goViewRecording"/>
        <descriptor href="#goWebinarSchedule"/>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Analytics and Reports States -->
    <descriptor id="AnalyticsDashboard" title="Analytics Dashboard" tag="analytics instructor-tools">
        <doc>A visual presentation of engagement and performance data for a course, helping instructors identify patterns and make informed decisions.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#analytics"/>
        <descriptor href="#student"/>
        <descriptor href="#course"/>
        <descriptor href="#goFilterAnalytics"/>
        <descriptor href="#doExportAnalytics"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCourseDetail"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="ReportCenter" title="Reporting Center" tag="analytics admin-tools">
        <doc>An administrative interface for generating, viewing, and exporting system-wide data compilations for institutional analysis and reporting.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#report"/>
        <descriptor href="#doGenerateReport"/>
        <descriptor href="#doExportReport"/>
        <descriptor href="#goReportDetail"/>
        <descriptor href="#goHome"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="ReportDetail" title="Report Detail Page" tag="analytics admin-tools">
        <doc>A comprehensive view of a specific data compilation, showing its contents in tabular, graphical, or downloadable formats.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#report"/>
        <descriptor href="#doExportReport"/>
        <descriptor href="#goReportCenter"/>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Accessibility and Settings -->
    <descriptor id="Settings" title="User Settings Page" tag="accessibility personalization">
        <doc>An interface where users configure their system preferences, including language, notifications, and accessibility accommodations.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#language"/>
        <descriptor href="#accessibilityFeature"/>
        <descriptor href="#userPreferences"/>
        <descriptor href="#doUpdateSettings"/>
        <descriptor href="#goUserProfile"/>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- States for External Content -->
    <descriptor id="WebinarView" title="Webinar Viewing Page" tag="communication synchronous media">
        <doc>The interface where users actively participate in a live session, with video, audio, chat, and interactive elements for real-time engagement.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#webinar"/>
        <descriptor href="#goWebinarDetail"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="RecordingView" title="Recording Viewing Page" tag="communication media">
        <doc>The interface where users play back captured sessions, with playback controls and navigation options for asynchronous viewing.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#webinarRecording"/>
        <descriptor href="#goWebinarDetail"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="MobileAccess" title="Mobile Application State" tag="mobile-access">
        <doc>The interface optimized for smartphone or tablet access, with adaptations for smaller screens and touch interaction plus offline capabilities.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#course"/>
        <descriptor href="#notification"/>
        <descriptor href="#offlineContent"/>
        <descriptor href="#doDownloadContent"/>
        <descriptor href="#doEnableNotifications"/>
        <descriptor href="#goHome"/>
        <descriptor href="#goCourseList"/>
        <descriptor href="#goEnrolledCourses"/>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- SECTION 3: STATE TRANSITIONS (CHOREOGRAPHY) -->

    <!-- Authentication Transitions -->
    <descriptor id="doLogin" type="unsafe" title="Login to System" rt="#Home" tag="authentication">
        <doc>Validates user credentials and, if successful, provides access to the system by creating an authenticated session.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doRegister" type="unsafe" title="Register New User" rt="#Login" tag="user-management">
        <doc>Creates a new user account in the system based on provided information, sending verification if required by policy.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#userName"/>
        <descriptor href="#userEmail"/>
        <descriptor href="#userPassword"/>
        <descriptor href="#userRole"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doResetPassword" type="unsafe" title="Reset Password" rt="#Login" tag="user-management security">
        <doc>Initiates the password recovery process by sending instructions to the user's registered email address.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#userEmail"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doLogout" type="idempotent" title="Logout from System" rt="#Login" tag="authentication">
        <doc>Terminates the user's active session, requiring re-authentication for further system access.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Navigation Transitions -->
    <descriptor id="goHome" type="safe" title="Go to Home Page" rt="#Home" tag="navigation">
        <doc>Redirects the user to their personalized dashboard, the primary entry point after authentication.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goLogin" type="safe" title="Go to Login Page" rt="#Login" tag="navigation authentication">
        <doc>Directs the user to the authentication screen where they can provide credentials for system access.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goRegister" type="safe" title="Go to Registration Page" rt="#Register" tag="navigation user-management">
        <doc>Directs the user to the account creation screen where new users can set up their system identity.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goSettings" type="safe" title="Go to Settings Page" rt="#Settings" tag="navigation personalization">
        <doc>Directs the user to the interface where they can customize their system preferences and configurations.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goReportCenter" type="safe" title="Go to Report Center" rt="#ReportCenter" tag="navigation analytics">
        <doc>Directs the user to the administrative interface for generating and viewing system-wide data reports.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goProgressDashboard" type="safe" title="Go to Progress Dashboard" rt="#ProgressDashboard" tag="navigation progress-tracking">
        <doc>Directs the user to the visual display of their course advancement and performance statistics.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goAnalyticsDashboard" type="safe" title="Go to Analytics Dashboard" rt="#AnalyticsDashboard" tag="navigation analytics">
        <doc>Directs the user to the data visualization interface showing engagement and performance metrics for a course.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goAnnouncementCreation" type="safe" title="Go to Announcement Creation" rt="#AnnouncementCreation" tag="navigation communication">
        <doc>Directs the instructor to the interface for composing and distributing messages to all course participants.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goGradebook" type="safe" title="Go to Gradebook" rt="#Gradebook" tag="navigation assessment">
        <doc>Directs the instructor to the comprehensive record of all student evaluations and calculated grades for a course.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goReportDetail" type="safe" title="Go to Report Detail" rt="#ReportDetail" tag="navigation analytics">
        <doc>Directs the user to the comprehensive view of a specific data compilation, identified by its unique reference.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#reportId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goUserProfile" type="safe" title="View User Profile" rt="#UserProfile" tag="navigation user-management">
        <doc>Directs the user to the interface displaying their personal information and account settings.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goUserList" type="safe" title="View User List" rt="#UserList" tag="navigation admin-tools">
        <doc>Directs the administrator to the interface displaying all system users with management options.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goUserDetail" type="safe" title="View User Details" rt="#UserDetail" tag="navigation admin-tools">
        <doc>Directs the administrator to the comprehensive view of a specific user's account, identified by their unique reference.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#userId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goCourseList" type="safe" title="View Course List" rt="#CourseList" tag="navigation course-management">
        <doc>Directs the user to the catalog of available courses with discovery and filtering options.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goCourseDetail" type="safe" title="View Course Details" rt="#CourseDetail" tag="navigation course-management">
        <doc>Directs the user to the comprehensive view of a specific course, identified by its unique reference.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goCreateCourse" type="safe" title="Go to Course Creation" rt="#CourseCreation" tag="navigation course-management">
        <doc>Directs the instructor to the interface for defining and configuring a new educational offering.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goEditCourse" type="safe" title="Go to Course Edit" rt="#CourseEdit" tag="navigation course-management">
        <doc>Directs the instructor to the interface for modifying an existing course's details and structure.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goModuleList" type="safe" title="View Module List" rt="#ModuleList" tag="navigation course-management">
        <doc>Directs the user to the listing of all thematic sections within a specific course.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goModuleDetail" type="safe" title="View Module Details" rt="#ModuleDetail" tag="navigation course-management">
        <doc>Directs the user to the comprehensive view of a specific thematic section, identified by its unique reference.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#moduleId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goCreateContent" type="safe" title="Go to Content Creation" rt="#ContentCreation" tag="navigation content-creation">
        <doc>Directs the instructor to the interface for producing new educational materials to be included in a module.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goContentDetail" type="safe" title="View Content Details" rt="#ContentDetail" tag="navigation content-creation">
        <doc>Directs the user to the comprehensive view of a specific educational resource, identified by its unique reference.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#contentId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goEnrolledCourses" type="safe" title="View Enrolled Courses" rt="#EnrolledCourses" tag="navigation enrollment">
        <doc>Directs the student to the personalized listing of courses they have registered for.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goAssignmentList" type="safe" title="View Assignment List" rt="#AssignmentList" tag="navigation assessment">
        <doc>Directs the user to the listing of all evaluation activities for a specific course.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goCreateAssignment" type="safe" title="Go to Assignment Creation" rt="#AssignmentCreation" tag="navigation assessment">
        <doc>Directs the instructor to the interface for defining a new evaluation activity for students.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goAssignmentDetail" type="safe" title="View Assignment Details" rt="#AssignmentDetail" tag="navigation assessment">
        <doc>Directs the user to the comprehensive view of a specific evaluation activity, identified by its unique reference.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#assignmentId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goSubmissionList" type="safe" title="View Submission List" rt="#SubmissionList" tag="navigation assessment">
        <doc>Directs the instructor to the listing of all student responses to a specific assignment.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#assignmentId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goSubmissionDetail" type="safe" title="View Submission Details" rt="#SubmissionDetail" tag="navigation assessment">
        <doc>Directs the user to the comprehensive view of a specific student's assignment response, identified by its unique reference.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#submissionId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goDiscussionList" type="safe" title="View Discussion List" rt="#DiscussionList" tag="navigation communication">
        <doc>Directs the user to the listing of all conversation forums for a specific course.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goDiscussionDetail" type="safe" title="View Discussion Details" rt="#DiscussionDetail" tag="navigation communication">
        <doc>Directs the user to the view of a specific conversation forum, identified by its unique reference.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#discussionId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goCreateDiscussion" type="safe" title="Go to Discussion Creation" rt="#DiscussionDetail" tag="navigation communication">
        <doc>Directs the user to the interface for starting a new conversation topic within a course.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goMessageCenter" type="safe" title="Go to Message Center" rt="#MessageCenter" tag="navigation communication">
        <doc>Directs the user to their unified inbox for personal communications within the system.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goCreateMessage" type="safe" title="Go to Create Message" rt="#MessageDetail" tag="navigation communication">
        <doc>Directs the user to the interface for composing a new personal communication to another system user.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goMessageDetail" type="safe" title="View Message Details" rt="#MessageDetail" tag="navigation communication">
        <doc>Directs the user to the view of a specific message exchange, identified by its unique reference.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#messageId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goGroupManagement" type="safe" title="Go to Group Management" rt="#GroupManagement" tag="navigation collaboration">
        <doc>Directs the instructor to the interface for creating and organizing student teams within a course.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goGroupDetail" type="safe" title="View Group Details" rt="#GroupDetail" tag="navigation collaboration">
        <doc>Directs the user to the comprehensive view of a specific student team, identified by its unique reference.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#groupId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goWebinarSchedule" type="safe" title="View Webinar Schedule" rt="#WebinarSchedule" tag="navigation communication">
        <doc>Directs the user to the calendar of planned live sessions for a specific course.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goWebinarDetail" type="safe" title="View Webinar Details" rt="#WebinarDetail" tag="navigation communication">
        <doc>Directs the user to the comprehensive view of a specific live session, identified by its unique reference.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#webinarId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goNotifications" type="safe" title="View Notifications" rt="#MessageCenter" tag="navigation communication">
        <doc>Directs the user to the listing of system messages and alerts generated by events and updates.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goClassProgress" type="safe" title="View Class Progress" rt="#ClassProgress" tag="navigation progress-tracking">
        <doc>Directs the instructor to the overview of all students' advancement and performance in a specific course.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goStudentProgress" type="safe" title="View Student Progress" rt="#StudentProgress" tag="navigation progress-tracking">
        <doc>Directs the instructor to the detailed view of a specific student's performance in a course, identified by both course and user references.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
        <descriptor href="#userId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Course Management Transitions -->
    <descriptor id="doCreateCourse" type="unsafe" title="Create New Course" rt="#CourseDetail" tag="course-management authoring">
        <doc>Generates a new educational offering in the system based on instructor-provided details and configuration settings.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseTitle"/>
        <descriptor href="#courseDescription"/>
        <descriptor href="#courseCategory"/>
        <descriptor href="#startDate"/>
        <descriptor href="#endDate"/>
        <descriptor href="#enrollmentCapacity"/>
        <descriptor href="#difficultyLevel"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doUpdateCourse" type="idempotent" title="Update Course" rt="#CourseDetail" tag="course-management authoring">
        <doc>Modifies an existing course's details, structure, or settings based on instructor inputs, preserving its identity and enrollment.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
        <descriptor href="#courseTitle"/>
        <descriptor href="#courseDescription"/>
        <descriptor href="#courseCategory"/>
        <descriptor href="#startDate"/>
        <descriptor href="#endDate"/>
        <descriptor href="#enrollmentCapacity"/>
        <descriptor href="#difficultyLevel"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doDeleteCourse" type="idempotent" title="Delete Course" rt="#CourseList" tag="course-management administration">
        <doc>Removes a course from the active catalog, potentially archiving its content and enrollment history for record-keeping.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doCreateModule" type="unsafe" title="Create Course Module" rt="#ModuleDetail" tag="course-management authoring">
        <doc>Generates a new thematic section within a course, establishing its place in the learning sequence and container for content.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
        <descriptor href="#moduleTitle"/>
        <descriptor href="#moduleDescription"/>
        <descriptor href="#moduleOrder"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doUpdateModule" type="idempotent" title="Update Module" rt="#ModuleDetail" tag="course-management authoring">
        <doc>Modifies an existing module's details, description, or sequence position within its parent course.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#moduleId"/>
        <descriptor href="#moduleTitle"/>
        <descriptor href="#moduleDescription"/>
        <descriptor href="#moduleOrder"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doDeleteModule" type="idempotent" title="Delete Module" rt="#ModuleList" tag="course-management authoring">
        <doc>Removes a thematic section from a course, potentially affecting its content items and the course's overall structure.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#moduleId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doCreateContent" type="unsafe" title="Create Content" rt="#ContentDetail" tag="content-creation authoring">
        <doc>Generates a new educational resource within a module, establishing its format, accessibility features, and learning material.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#moduleId"/>
        <descriptor href="#contentTitle"/>
        <descriptor href="#contentDescription"/>
        <descriptor href="#contentType"/>
        <descriptor href="#contentData"/>
        <descriptor href="#contentAccessibility"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doUpdateContent" type="idempotent" title="Update Content" rt="#ContentDetail" tag="content-creation authoring">
        <doc>Modifies an existing educational resource's details, material, or accessibility features while maintaining its position in the course structure.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#contentId"/>
        <descriptor href="#contentTitle"/>
        <descriptor href="#contentDescription"/>
        <descriptor href="#contentType"/>
        <descriptor href="#contentData"/>
        <descriptor href="#contentAccessibility"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doDeleteContent" type="idempotent" title="Delete Content" rt="#ModuleDetail" tag="content-creation authoring">
        <doc>Removes an educational resource from its parent module, affecting the module's completeness and potentially student progress tracking.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#contentId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doSaveDraftCourse" type="idempotent" title="Save Course as Draft" rt="#CourseEdit" tag="course-management workflow">
        <doc>Preserves the current state of a course in development without making it visible to students or available for enrollment.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doSaveDraftContent" type="idempotent" title="Save Content as Draft" rt="#ContentCreation" tag="content-creation workflow">
        <doc>Preserves the current state of an educational resource in development without publishing it to students in the module.</doc>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goPreviewContent" type="safe" title="Preview Content" rt="#ContentDetail" tag="content-creation authoring">
        <doc>Displays an educational resource as it will appear to students, allowing instructors to verify its presentation before publishing.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#contentId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doPublishCourse" type="idempotent" title="Publish Course" rt="#CourseDetail" tag="course-management workflow">
        <doc>Makes a course visible in the catalog and available for enrollment, transitioning it from draft to active status.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Enrollment Transitions -->
    <descriptor id="doEnrollCourse" type="unsafe" title="Enroll in Course" rt="#EnrolledCourses" tag="enrollment student">
        <doc>Registers a student for a specific course, granting access to its materials and adding it to their enrolled courses list.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
        <descriptor href="#userId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doUnenrollCourse" type="idempotent" title="Unenroll from Course" rt="#EnrolledCourses" tag="enrollment student">
        <doc>Removes a student's registration from a course, potentially affecting their access to materials and progress records.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
        <descriptor href="#userId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doExtendDeadline" type="idempotent" title="Extend Deadline" rt="#StudentProgress" tag="assessment instructor-tools">
        <doc>Grants a specific student additional time for course completion beyond the standard end date, accommodating special circumstances.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
        <descriptor href="#userId"/>
        <descriptor href="#endDate"/>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Assignment Transitions -->
    <descriptor id="doCreateAssignment" type="unsafe" title="Create Assignment" rt="#AssignmentDetail" tag="assessment instructor-tools">
        <doc>Generates a new evaluation activity within a course, establishing its requirements, deadlines, and assessment parameters.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
        <descriptor href="#assignmentTitle"/>
        <descriptor href="#assignmentDescription"/>
        <descriptor href="#assignmentType"/>
        <descriptor href="#dueDate"/>
        <descriptor href="#maxScore"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doUpdateAssignment" type="idempotent" title="Update Assignment" rt="#AssignmentDetail" tag="assessment instructor-tools">
        <doc>Modifies an existing evaluation activity's details, requirements, or parameters while maintaining its identity and submissions.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#assignmentId"/>
        <descriptor href="#assignmentTitle"/>
        <descriptor href="#assignmentDescription"/>
        <descriptor href="#assignmentType"/>
        <descriptor href="#dueDate"/>
        <descriptor href="#maxScore"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doDeleteAssignment" type="idempotent" title="Delete Assignment" rt="#AssignmentList" tag="assessment instructor-tools">
        <doc>Removes an evaluation activity from a course, potentially affecting its grade calculations and student submissions.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#assignmentId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doCreateRubric" type="unsafe" title="Create Grading Rubric" rt="#AssignmentDetail" tag="assessment instructor-tools">
        <doc>Establishes a structured scoring tool for an assignment, defining the dimensions and performance levels for evaluation.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#assignmentId"/>
        <descriptor href="#rubricTitle"/>
        <descriptor href="#rubricCriteria"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doSubmitAssignment" type="unsafe" title="Submit Assignment" rt="#AssignmentDetail" tag="assessment student">
        <doc>Records a student's response to an evaluation activity, capturing their work for instructor review and grading.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#assignmentId"/>
        <descriptor href="#submissionContent"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doGradeSubmission" type="idempotent" title="Grade Submission" rt="#SubmissionDetail" tag="assessment instructor-tools">
        <doc>Evaluates a student's assignment response, assigning a score and potentially providing explanatory feedback.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#submissionId"/>
        <descriptor href="#gradeValue"/>
        <descriptor href="#feedback"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doProvideFeedback" type="idempotent" title="Provide Feedback" rt="#SubmissionDetail" tag="assessment instructor-tools">
        <doc>Adds or updates instructional comments on a student's work, offering guidance without necessarily changing the grade.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#submissionId"/>
        <descriptor href="#feedback"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doExportGrades" type="idempotent" title="Export Grades" rt="#Gradebook" tag="assessment instructor-tools">
        <doc>Generates a downloadable file containing student scores for a course, formatted for use in external systems.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doCalculateOverallGrades" type="safe" title="Calculate Overall Grades" rt="#Gradebook" tag="assessment instructor-tools">
        <doc>Computes final course grades by applying weightings to individual assignment scores according to the grading scheme.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Communication Transitions -->
    <descriptor id="doCreateDiscussion" type="unsafe" title="Create Discussion" rt="#DiscussionDetail" tag="communication collaboration">
        <doc>Establishes a new conversation forum within a course, defining its topic and initial prompt for participation.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
        <descriptor href="#discussionTitle"/>
        <descriptor href="#discussionDescription"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doCreatePost" type="unsafe" title="Create Discussion Post" rt="#DiscussionDetail" tag="communication collaboration">
        <doc>Adds a new message to a conversation forum, initiating a thread or starting a new topic for discussion.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#discussionId"/>
        <descriptor href="#postContent"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doReplyToPost" type="unsafe" title="Reply to Post" rt="#DiscussionDetail" tag="communication collaboration">
        <doc>Adds a response to an existing message in a conversation forum, continuing the thread of discussion.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#postId"/>
        <descriptor href="#postContent"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doCreateAnnouncement" type="unsafe" title="Create Announcement" rt="#CourseDetail" tag="communication instructor-tools">
        <doc>Broadcasts a system message to all participants in a course, notifying them of important information or updates.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
        <descriptor href="#notificationContent"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doReplyToMessage" type="unsafe" title="Reply to Message" rt="#MessageDetail" tag="communication personal">
        <doc>Responds to a personal communication from another user, continuing the private conversation thread.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#messageId"/>
        <descriptor href="#messageContent"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doAttachFile" type="unsafe" title="Attach File to Message" rt="#MessageDetail" tag="communication media">
        <doc>Includes a document or media resource with a personal communication, making it available to the recipient.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#messageId"/>
        <descriptor href="#messageAttachments"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doCreateGroup" type="unsafe" title="Create Student Group" rt="#GroupDetail" tag="collaboration instructor-tools">
        <doc>Establishes a new team of students within a course, defining its membership and collaborative workspace.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
        <descriptor href="#groupName"/>
        <descriptor href="#groupMembers"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doUpdateGroup" type="idempotent" title="Update Group" rt="#GroupDetail" tag="collaboration instructor-tools">
        <doc>Modifies an existing student team's details or settings while maintaining its identity and workspace.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#groupId"/>
        <descriptor href="#groupName"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doDeleteGroup" type="idempotent" title="Delete Group" rt="#GroupManagement" tag="collaboration instructor-tools">
        <doc>Removes a student team from a course, potentially affecting collaborative assignments and workspace access.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#groupId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doAddGroupMember" type="unsafe" title="Add Group Member" rt="#GroupDetail" tag="collaboration instructor-tools">
        <doc>Includes an additional student in an existing team, granting them access to its collaborative workspace.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#groupId"/>
        <descriptor href="#userId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doRemoveGroupMember" type="idempotent" title="Remove Group Member" rt="#GroupDetail" tag="collaboration instructor-tools">
        <doc>Excludes a student from a team, revoking their access to its collaborative workspace and activities.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#groupId"/>
        <descriptor href="#userId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doCreateWebinar" type="unsafe" title="Create Webinar" rt="#WebinarDetail" tag="communication synchronous instructor-tools">
        <doc>Schedules a new live session for a course, establishing its timing, access details, and topic.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
        <descriptor href="#webinarTitle"/>
        <descriptor href="#webinarDescription"/>
        <descriptor href="#webinarDate"/>
        <descriptor href="#webinarDuration"/>
        <descriptor href="#webinarUrl"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doUpdateWebinar" type="idempotent" title="Update Webinar" rt="#WebinarDetail" tag="communication synchronous instructor-tools">
        <doc>Modifies an existing live session's details, timing, or access information while maintaining its identity.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#webinarId"/>
        <descriptor href="#webinarTitle"/>
        <descriptor href="#webinarDescription"/>
        <descriptor href="#webinarDate"/>
        <descriptor href="#webinarDuration"/>
        <descriptor href="#webinarUrl"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doDeleteWebinar" type="idempotent" title="Delete Webinar" rt="#WebinarSchedule" tag="communication synchronous instructor-tools">
        <doc>Cancels a planned live session, removing it from the course schedule and notifying potential participants.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#webinarId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doJoinWebinar" type="idempotent" title="Join Webinar" rt="#WebinarView" tag="communication synchronous">
        <doc>Connects a user to an active live session, enabling their real-time participation through video, audio, or chat.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#webinarId"/>
        <descriptor href="#webinarUrl"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goViewRecording" type="safe" title="View Webinar Recording" rt="#RecordingView" tag="communication media">
        <doc>Directs the user to the playback interface for a captured live session, allowing asynchronous viewing.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#webinarId"/>
        <descriptor href="#webinarRecording"/>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Analytics Transitions -->
    <descriptor id="goFilterAnalytics" type="safe" title="Filter Analytics Data" rt="#AnalyticsDashboard" tag="analytics instructor-tools">
        <doc>Adjusts the parameters of displayed engagement and performance metrics to focus on specific timeframes or aspects.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
        <descriptor href="#startDate"/>
        <descriptor href="#endDate"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doExportAnalytics" type="idempotent" title="Export Analytics Data" rt="#AnalyticsDashboard" tag="analytics instructor-tools">
        <doc>Generates a downloadable file containing engagement and performance metrics for a course, formatted for external analysis.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doGenerateReport" type="unsafe" title="Generate System Report" rt="#ReportDetail" tag="analytics admin-tools">
        <doc>Creates a new data compilation based on specified parameters, processing system information for institutional analysis.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#reportTitle"/>
        <descriptor href="#reportType"/>
        <descriptor href="#startDate"/>
        <descriptor href="#endDate"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doExportReport" type="idempotent" title="Export Report Data" rt="#ReportDetail" tag="analytics admin-tools">
        <doc>Generates a downloadable file containing report information, formatted for use in external systems or presentations.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#reportId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Filter Transitions -->
    <descriptor id="goFilterCourses" type="safe" title="Filter Course List" rt="#CourseList" tag="navigation course-management">
        <doc>Adjusts the parameters of displayed courses to show only those matching specific criteria for more targeted browsing.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseCategory"/>
        <descriptor href="#instructor"/>
        <descriptor href="#courseStatus"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goFilterStudents" type="safe" title="Filter Student List" rt="#ClassProgress" tag="navigation instructor-tools">
        <doc>Adjusts the parameters of displayed students to show only those matching specific criteria for focused monitoring.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goFilterAssignments" type="safe" title="Filter Assignment List" rt="#AssignmentList" tag="navigation assessment">
        <doc>Adjusts the parameters of displayed assignments to show only those matching specific criteria for targeted management.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
        <descriptor href="#dueDate"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goFilterSubmissions" type="safe" title="Filter Submission List" rt="#SubmissionList" tag="navigation assessment">
        <doc>Adjusts the parameters of displayed student responses to show only those matching specific status criteria for focused grading.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#assignmentId"/>
        <descriptor href="#submissionStatus"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goFilterDiscussions" type="safe" title="Filter Discussion List" rt="#DiscussionList" tag="navigation communication">
        <doc>Adjusts the parameters of displayed conversation forums to show only those matching specific criteria for targeted participation.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#courseId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="goFilterMessages" type="safe" title="Filter Messages" rt="#MessageCenter" tag="navigation communication">
        <doc>Adjusts the parameters of displayed personal communications to show only those matching specific senders or dates for focused review.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#messageSender"/>
        <descriptor href="#messageDate"/>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- User Management Transitions -->
    <descriptor id="doUpdateProfile" type="idempotent" title="Update User Profile" rt="#UserProfile" tag="user-management personalization">
        <doc>Modifies a user's personal information or system preferences while maintaining their account identity and history.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#userName"/>
        <descriptor href="#userEmail"/>
        <descriptor href="#userPassword"/>
        <descriptor href="#userPreferences"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doCreateUser" type="unsafe" title="Create User" rt="#UserDetail" tag="user-management admin-tools">
        <doc>Establishes a new account in the system, defining the user's identity, contact information, and access permissions.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#userName"/>
        <descriptor href="#userEmail"/>
        <descriptor href="#userPassword"/>
        <descriptor href="#userRole"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doUpdateUser" type="idempotent" title="Update User" rt="#UserDetail" tag="user-management admin-tools">
        <doc>Administratively modifies a user's account details or permissions while preserving their identity and history.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#userId"/>
        <descriptor href="#userName"/>
        <descriptor href="#userEmail"/>
        <descriptor href="#userRole"/>
        <descriptor href="#adminPermissions"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doDeleteUser" type="idempotent" title="Delete User" rt="#UserList" tag="user-management admin-tools">
        <doc>Removes a user account from the active system, potentially preserving their data for record-keeping or compliance.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#userId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Settings Transitions -->
    <descriptor id="doUpdateSettings" type="idempotent" title="Update Settings" rt="#Settings" tag="accessibility personalization">
        <doc>Modifies a user's system configuration preferences, including interface language, notifications, and accessibility accommodations.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#language"/>
        <descriptor href="#accessibilityFeature"/>
        <descriptor href="#userPreferences"/>
    </descriptor>

    <!-- Mobile Transitions -->
    <descriptor id="doDownloadContent" type="unsafe" title="Download Content for Offline Access" rt="#MobileAccess" tag="mobile-access">
        <doc>Saves course materials to a mobile device's local storage, making them available for review without an active internet connection.</doc>
        <descriptor href="#contentId"/>
    </descriptor>

    <descriptor id="doEnableNotifications" type="idempotent" title="Enable Mobile Notifications" rt="#MobileAccess" tag="mobile-access communication">
        <doc>Configures a mobile device to receive system alerts as push notifications, even when the application is not actively open.</doc>
    </descriptor>

</alps>
